thehendonmob.com 2018-09-16

# The Hendon Mob Privacy Policy - The Hendon Mob

Last Updated: 15th of April 2014

The Hendon Mob (“The Hendon Mob/us/we/our”) is committed to protecting the privacy of its users (“users” or “you”). For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (“Act”), the data controller is Mediarex Enterprises Ltd, British Virgin Island registered company N°1701449, 2nd  Floor, Yamraj Building, Road Town, Tortola, British Virgin. This Privacy Policy has been created to inform you about how The Hendon Mob manages, collects, stores and uses the information you provide in connection with the thehendonmob.com website, forums and/or any related services (collectively “Service(s)”).

By visiting or otherwise using any of our Services, you consent to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy, the terms of which are expressly incorporated by reference into The Hendon Mob Terms of Use.

**Revised Terms**

We may, from time to time, revise this Privacy Policy, and the date of last revision will be available at the top of this page.  **Your continued use of the Service after changes have been posted to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes,** so please be sure to check periodically that you have read the latest version.

**No Users Under 18**

The Hendon Mob’s Services are not intended for use by individuals under 18 (eighteen) years of age. No one under the age of 18 may provide any personal information to or on the Service. We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 18. If you are under 18, please do not register on the Service or send any information about you to us. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from an individual under 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about anyone under 18, please contact us at [support@thehendonmob.com](mailto:support@thehendonmob.com).

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
The information we collect from you allows you to use our Services, it also enables us to improve and provide relevant, enhanced Services to you and thereby improve your user experience.

Information We Collect Directly From You.

If you subscribe to our emails, or open a user account directly with The Hendon Mob, we collect the information you provide to us, namely email address, name, address, age.

The Hendon Mob also acquires information about you via (i) your access and participation in message boards, chat rooms, and/or forums on the Service, and (ii) contents of your Customer Support requests.

Other information The Hendon Mob may collect includes your occupation, language, zip code, area code, location, and the time zone where a Service is used, as well as information about your computer, mobile device, software, platform, incident data, Internet Protocol (IP) address, network Media Access Control (MAC) address and connection, browser type, browser language, and/or information relating to you use and browsing habits, so that The Hendon Mob can better understand customer behavior and improve its products, services, and advertising.

**Use of Your Information**

**How The Hendon Mob Uses Your Information**

The Hendon Mob uses your information to fulfill your specific requests. In addition, the personal information you provide will allow The Hendon Mob to send to you or respond to your e-mails, inquiries or requests; to notify you about information regarding The Hendon Mob, the Services, or a third party service that may be of interest to you; to enable you to receive personalized content; for the purposes for which you provided the information; to improve the content and navigability of the Services; to alert you to new features, special events, products and services, as well as for marketing and promotional purposes. You may also later opt out of certain of these communications.

We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with the Services; to customize the advertising and content you see, including the display of targeted advertisements; to generate anonymous and/or aggregated reporting; in the collection of your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes; to administer loyalty programs, tailor its offerings, or web pages and to enforce the legal terms that govern your use of the Services and/or your relationship to us.

We may use your personal information that we collect to create anonymous and/or aggregated data, and we may also combine personal information with other information for this purpose. The Hendon Mob reserves the right to create, use, and disclose anonymous and/or aggregated data for any reason, without limitation, and such derivative data is not subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We may share your personal information with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

**What The Hendon Mob Does Not Do with Your Information**

The information that you provide to The Hendon Mob will not be disclosed, rented, leased, sold or otherwise distributed to unaffiliated third parties, and will be used only for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

**Where we store your data**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. The Hendon Mob will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Refer A Friend; Friend Finder Tools**

If you choose to use a referral service to “tell a friend” about a Service, whether directly via the Service or via a social network service (“SNS”), such tools will help you find your contacts and allow your contacts to associate your Service account with your social networking profile and/or email address. The Hendon Mob may ask you for your friend’s name and email address. The Hendon Mob will send your friend an email on your behalf or a text message inviting him or her to visit the relevant site or visit the Service. The Hendon Mob stores your friend’s name and email for the purpose of sending this email and for redundancy checking (to be sure that your friend does not receive multiple copies of the same email message). Your resulting friend’s list and information will be subject to this Privacy Policy. The Hendon Mob does not keep or use this information for any other purpose.

**Promotions; Contests; Sweepstakes – Publicity Waiver**

If you enter into a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion (“Promotion”), The Hendon Mob may use the information you provide to administer those Promotions. By accepting any prize from the Service, you agree to allow us to publish, print, broadcast and use, worldwide, in any media at any time, now or hereafter created, your name, picture, voice, likeness, and/or biographical information for promotional purposes without additional compensation and execute such releases as we may require for this purpose.

**User Contributions**

You are responsible for any content, including personal information, that you contribute to be posted, published or displayed on the Service, or in its chat rooms, blogs, message boards, user “profiles” for public view, or in similar forums on its sites through mobile services and/or through third party sites or services. (collectively “User Contributions”).  Information that you disclose in any of these forums is public information, and as such you can have no expectation of privacy or confidentiality.

The Hendon Mob cannot control the actions of other users of the Services with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions; therefore, we cannot guarantee who will view your User Contributions. We are not responsible for circumvention by third parties of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Service.

You understand and acknowledge that in relation to The Hendon Mob, that under The Hendon Mob’s Terms of Service, you have granted The Hendon Mob a license to use, modify and publish your User Contribution. You also understand and acknowledge that even after removal, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or may have been copied or stored by other Service users or other third parties. Proper access and use of information provided on or through the Services, including User Contributions, is governed by this Privacy Policy and The Hendon Mob’s Terms of Use and known or suspected violations should be reported to [support@thehendonmob.com](mailto:support@thehendonmob.com).

**Third Party Service Providers**

The Hendon Mob may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate its Services, to provide the Services on its behalf, to perform tasks (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Services) or to assist The Hendon Mob in analyzing how its Services are used.

The Hendon Mob may employ third party contractors to collect personal information on its behalf to provide email delivery, product, prize or Promotions fulfillment & administration, or other services through the Service. When requesting these services, you may be asked to supply your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address to its contractors. The Hendon Mob may ask some third party contractors, data analytics or market research firms, to supplement personal information that you provide to The Hendon Mob for its own marketing and demographic studies, so that The Hendon Mob can consistently improve its sites and related advertising to better meet its users needs and preferences. To enrich its understanding of individual customers, The Hendon Mob may tie this information to the information you provide to it.

**Other Data Collection**

**Cookies**  
Like many other Services, The Hendon Mob may use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer’s hard disk or your mobile device for record-keeping purposes. The Service may send cookies to a computer or a mobile device when a user accesses or views a Service. Information contained in a cookie may be linked to personal information for purposes such as improving the quality of The Hendon Mob’s Service, tailoring recommendations to interests, and making the Service easier to use. Third party advertisers on the Services may also place or read cookies on your browser. Cookies can be disabled at any time by changing your web browser’s options to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the services, websites and/ or applications that you visit or use. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions or functionalities of the Service.

**Web Beacons**

The Hendon Mob may allow ad networks, such as third party ad servers and ad agencies, to serve advertisements within our Services. We may also place web beacons for these companies within our pages. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these third parties can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

**Third Party Links; Sites**

The Service may contain links to third parties’ services, websites or applications. The fact that the Service links to a third party’s service, website or application or presents a banner ad or other type of advertisement does not mean that The Hendon Mob endorses or authorizes that third party, nor is it a representation by The Hendon Mob of any affiliation with that third party. If you click on a link to a third party site or application, including on an advertisement, you will leave The Hendon Mob site or Service you are visiting or application you are running and will go to the site or application linked to. These third party services, websites and applications may place their own cookies or other files on your computer or mobile device, and may collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites and applications follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. Because The Hendon Mob cannot control the activities of third parties, it cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and it cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as The Hendon Mob. You are therefore encouraged to read the privacy policies or statements of other services, websites and applications you visit before providing any personal information.

**Disclosure of Information**

You understand and agree that The Hendon Mob may be required to disclose personal information if required to do so by law, or if it is in The Hendon Mob’s unfettered belief that such disclosure is necessary to avoid liability, to comply with any legal or regulatory process, to protect the property and rights of The Hendon Mob or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity The Hendon Mob may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable. Note that The Hendon Mob is not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that it may receive.

The Hendon Mob may also disclose information about you if it determines that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce the terms and conditions of the Service or to protect its operations or users. In the future, you accept that we may sell some or all of our assets. In such transactions, generally customer information is one of the transferred business assets. The Hendon Mob may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personal information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy; in the event of a sale of our assets including our database, customer information will be transferred.

**Changing or Deleting Your Information**

**The Hendon Mob Account**

You may review, update, correct or delete any personal information by changing the applicable information in your profile page of your The Hendon Mob account or by sending us an email – detailing your account ID – to [support@thehendonmob.com](mailto:support@thehendonmob.com). If you completely delete all of this information, your account may be deactivated.

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

If you would like The Hendon Mob to delete your record in its system, please contact The Hendon Mob and it will attempt to accommodate, your request within a reasonable time period, if The Hendon Mob is not legally obligated to retain the record.

**Unsubscribing**

In each and every email that we send to you, there is an ‘unsubscribe’ hyperlink, which you may you use if you wish to ‘opt out’ of and stop receiving email communications from us.  The hyperlink will direct you to our Service, where upon entering the email address that you no longer wish to receive our emails; one last confirmation email shall then be sent to the email address you designate.  Merely confirm that you do indeed wish to stop our email’s being sent to you and that email address shall, within a reasonable time period, be automatically removed from receiving our emails.

**Removal Requests**

It is The Hendon Mob’s policy to remove players from the GPI database only in very limited circumstances. In the unlikely event that The Hendon Mob agrees (in its unfettered discretion) to such removal, The Hendon Mob reserves the right to charge a fee in order to cover, without limitation, its administrative and technical expenses. The removal fee must be paid in full and in advance before any removal request occurs.

**Security**

The Hendon Mob has made reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, The Hendon Mob cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to overcome those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. Also please note that email and messaging systems are not considered secure, so The Hendon Mob discourages you from sending The Hendon Mob personal information through these media.

**Contacting Us**

For any questions about its Privacy Policy or any other issue please contact The Hendon Mob at: [support@thehendonmob.com](mailto:support@thehendonmob.com).
